International Relations, News and Views UP227
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
International Relations, News and Views
2001 -- 2008
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
International Relations Program
UP227
0.5 Linear Feet
27 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of International Relations, News and Views. It is the newsletter of the Tufts Program in International Relations. It features articles about IR community events, student and faculty research, and the professional paths of IR alumni. Published quarterly; series may contain 3 or 4 issues per academic year.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Program in International Relations was created in 1977 with the expressed purpose of preparing undergraduates for the rigors of graduate school in international affairs. In that inaugural year under its first director, Professor John S. Gibson of the Political Science Department, the program enrolled twenty-seven students. In 2010, the Program in International Relations has over six hundred declared majors and a national reputation.
- International Relations, News and Views, 2001 -- 2008; UP227.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 27 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of International Relations, News and Views, the newsletter of the Tufts Program in International Relations. It features articles about IR community events, student and faculty research, and the professional paths of IR alumni. Published quarterly; series may contain 3 or 4 issues per academic year.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2001; UP227.001.001.00001; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2002; UP227.001.001.00002; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    1, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2002; UP227.001.001.00003; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    1, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2002; UP227.001.001.00004; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    2, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall [2], 2002; UP227.001.001.00005; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    2, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2003; UP227.001.001.00006; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    2, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2003; UP227.001.001.00007; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    2, 4
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2003; UP227.001.001.00008; Tufts Program in International Relations
    3, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2004; UP227.001.001.00009; Tufts Program in International Relations (Box 1)
    3, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2004; UP227.001.001.00010; Tufts Program in International Relations
    3, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2004; UP227.001.001.00011; Tufts Program in International Relations
    4, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall [2], 2004; UP227.001.001.00012; Tufts Program in International Relations
    4, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2005; UP227.001.001.00013; Tufts Program in International Relations
    4, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2005; UP227.001.001.00014; Tufts Program in International Relations
    4, 4
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2005; UP227.001.001.00015; Tufts Program in International Relations
    5, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall [2], 2005; UP227.001.001.00016; Tufts Program in International Relations
    5, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2006; UP227.001.001.00017; Tufts Program in International Relations
    5, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2006; UP227.001.001.00018; Tufts Program in International Relations
    5, 4
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2006; UP227.001.001.00019; Tufts Program in International Relations
    6, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall [2], 2006; UP227.001.001.00020; Tufts Program in International Relations
    6, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2007; UP227.001.001.00021; Tufts Program in International Relations
    6, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2007; UP227.001.001.00022; Tufts Program in International Relations
    6, 4
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2007; UP227.001.001.00023; Tufts Program in International Relations
    7, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall [2], 2007; UP227.001.001.00024; Tufts Program in International Relations
    7, 2
  - International Relations, News and Views, Winter, 2008; UP227.001.001.00025; Tufts Program in International Relations
    7, 3
  - International Relations, News and Views, Spring, 2008; UP227.001.001.00026; Tufts Program in International Relations
    7, 4
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall, 2008; UP227.001.001.00027; Tufts Program in International Relations
    8, 1
  - International Relations, News and Views, Fall [2], 2008; UP227.001.001.00028; Tufts Program in International Relations
    8, 2